http://www.surf-one.com/privacy/

Skate OneWelcome Log In or RegisterPowell-PeraltaBones BrigadeBones BearingsBONES WHEELSMini LogoAera Trucks My AccountMy WishlistMy CartCheckout Search:
GO
Shop Search Account Cart
Shop Online:
Completes
View All Completes
Street / Park
Mini
Decks
View All Decks
Flight
Pro Series
C-Cut
A.W.O.L.
Trucks
View All Trucks
Sub Assemblies
Trucks
Truck Parts
Bearings
Clothing
View All Clothing
New Products
Free shipping on orders over $60 • $6.50 shipping for orders under $60 • Click for details
Free shipping on orders $60+ • $6.50 shipping for orders $60- • details Free shipping on orders $60+ • see detailsFree Shipping InfoSkate One currently offers free shipping for all domestic orders over $60 and a flat fee of $6.50 for all orders under $60 inside the United States (Alaska and Hawaii excluded). Certain heavy or oversized items may be excluded from free shipping.Online shipping rates are for online orders only and do not apply to phone orders or mail orders. View our shipping and delivery page for full details Close
Production is running, demand is high, products will be coming in so check back often. Holiday shipping info. READ BEFORE ORDERINGOrders must be received and clear credit authorization by 12:00 p.m. (noon) PST, or your order may not be processed until the following business day.Holiday Shipping Info:Orders are shipped on business days only.Business days are Monday-Friday, excluding Nov 26-27, Dec 24-25, Dec 30-31, 2020, Jan 1, 2021. Close
Customer ServiceCareer OpportunitiesAbout UsContact UsFrequently Asked QuestionsOrdering InformationReturn PolicyShipping & DeliveryWarranty InformationDealer LocatorMailing ListsManufacturingPrivacy PolicyTerms Of UseReward Points FAQReward Points PolicySkate One Privacy PolicySkate One is committed to respecting your privacy. We believe in the “Golden Rule” and we apply it to all our interactions with our customers. Any personally identifiable information that you give us or we collect as you use our sites will only be used internally to improve our products, services, and to provide you with a better browsing experience. We do not disclose, sell or trade personal information to third parties. This Privacy Statement was created to let you know how we collect information from you on this website, and how we use it, but don’t abuse it.Personally Identifiable InformationThe personal information we collect when you use our site may include your name, mailing address, phone number, e-mail address and credit card information if you purchase from us. We request some of this information when you register your Skate One products online. We also request this information when you enter a contest, participate in other promotional activities or purchase product from us, so we can administer the contest, notify winners, ship the product to you, etc. We may also ask you to fill out a survey to assist us in getting to know you and your preferences better.Cookies And IP AddressesA “cookie” is a small data file transferred by a Web site server to your computer’s hard drive. Most Web browsers will automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to refuse cookies. If you turn off cookies, most of the features on our site will still be available. Accepting cookies allows us to identify your computer, but it does not give us access to your personally identifiable information. The information we collect from cookies is used to analyze traffic patterns on our Site. If you arrived at our Web site via a link from another site, we may receive aggregate or otherwise anonymous information about your visit to our site. This helps us improve our site content and makes the site easier to use. Skate One also logs IP addresses, or the location of computers on the Internet, to help diagnose problems with our server and to help administer the Site. This information is also considered confidential by SOC.Skate One’s Contest Policy, Including Its Policy For Kids(Individuals under 18 years of age)Skate One conducts contests and give-aways on its Web site. You may be asked to provide your personal contact information or answer a survey in order to enter. Survey results will be tabulated in aggregate form and will not be used to identify individual information. Contest winners are randomly selected and will be notified through the contact information they provide. Contest winners must then print out a downloadable form found on the Skate One web site and fill it out and send it to the address provided on the form. If the winner is under the age of 18, his or her parent or guardian must give their parental consent and fill out the form. Upon receipt of the completed form, Skate One will send the winner the prize.Your ConsentBy using Skate One’s site, you consent to the collection, use, and storage of your information by us in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we do make changes to our Privacy Policy, we will post it on this page. Get Propaganda Name
Email
Subscribe
Follow @SkateOneCorp
Skate One 6860 Cortona Drive Unit B Goleta, CA. 93117 Phone: (800) 288-7528 Fax: (805) 964-0511 info@SkateOne.com
Quick Links:New ProductsAbout UsManufacturingDealer LocatorMailing ListsBlogForumContact UsFacebookFAQ'sOrdering InfoShipping & DeliveryWarranty InfoReturn PolicyGift Card BalanceSite MapCareer OpportunitiesReward Points Our Sites:Powell-PeraltaBones BearingsBONES WHEELSMini-LogoAera TrucksGolden DragonBones BrigadeAnimal Chin
©2020 Skate One. All Rights Reserved. | Privacy Policy
